// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: " When does Exceptions in Java arises in code sequence?",
  answer: "Run Time",
  options: [
    "Run Time",
   "Compilation Time",
 "Can Occur Any Time",
 "None of the mentioned"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "Which of these keywords is not a part of exception handling?",
  answer: "thrown",
  options: [
    "try",
    "finally",
    "thrown",
    "catch"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "Which of these keywords must be used to monitor for exceptions?",
  answer: "try",
  options: [
    "try",
    "finally",
    "throw",
    "catch"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "Which is the superclass of Error class in Java?",
     answer: "Throwbale",
  options: [
    "RuntimeException",
    "Throwable",
    "Exception",
    "None of the above"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: " Which of these keywords is used to manually throw an exception?" ,
  answer: "throw",
  options: [
    "try",
    "finally",
    "throw",
    "catch"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: " 'finally' block will never execute if the 'catch' block is missing. Select True or False" ,
  answer: "False",
  options: [
    "True",
    "False",
   
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: " 'throws' keyword is used to ______" ,
  answer: "Propagate the exception to the caller of the method",
  options: [
    "Propagate the exception to the caller of the method",
    "Define a new exception type",
    "Throw an exception explicitly",
    "None of the above"
  ]
},

{
  numb: 8,
  question: " All exceptions in java are derived from ________" ,
  answer: "Throwable class",
  options: [
    "Throwable class",
    "Exception class",
    "Error class",
    "None of the above"
  ]
},

{
  numb: 9,
  question: "FileInputStream implements which interface for closing file automatically in java7?" ,
  answer: "java.lang.AutoCloseable",
  options: [
    "java.lang.AutoClose",
    "java.lang.CloseAutomatically",
    "java.lang.AutoCloseable",
    "java.lang.Closeable"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: " .What type of Exceptions can be ignored at compile time?" ,
  answer: "	Runtime",
  options: [
    "	Runtime",
    "Checked",
    "Both",
    "None" 
   ]
},



// you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
// but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

//   {
//   numb: 6,
//   question: "Your Question is Here",
//   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
//   options: [
//     "Option 1",
//     "option 2",
//     "option 3",
//     "option 4"
//   ]
// },
];